Paid in full equals better results.
Monthly is dipping your toe in
and never fully committing.
This is bullshit lingo you've got from
your coach.
And I replied to it and I said, "Look,
I am not against paid in
full, but for coaching,
I think it's fucked,"
and I'll give you some reasons.
Number one, paid in full benefits you,
not your client.
Not your client, ever. You say commitment,
but really, I guarantee,
Coach fucking Akos,
if I went into your life, "Hey,
do you pay for Netflix
paid in full?" "No, I pay monthly." "Oh,
do you pay for Spotify annually?" "No, I
pay monthly." Oh,
when you join my fucking mentorship,
you're the one
begging for a split pay. Why?
It's not cost, it's cash flow.
So why is it in your life you don't like
fucking paying for anything up front and
you use PayPal pay in full, but why
is it in your client's life they've got to
pay
you in full for commitment? This
is bullshit double standards.
It's fucked and you know it.
Everything that you proclaim as a
business, me, me,
me, me, me,
everything you build should be client
fucking centric.
It should be about making it easier for
them.
And here's the reality, I'm sorry,
Coach Akos, if you did weekly or monthly,
it'll
benefit your client more.
You'll get way more sales from it,
and you want them to
be able to dip their toe.
That's a good thing because a lot of the
market will
not commit to six months because not cash,
not a waste
cash,
because they think you're fucking shit at
what you do.
And sometimes people want to try before
they buy